<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<param>
	<text description="Frequency greater" help="freq1">
		<name>freq1</name>
	</text>
	<text description="Frequency less " help="freq2">
		<name>freq2</name>
	</text>
	<text description="Select miRNA-like DB" value="miRNA" help="DB">
		<name>DB</name>
	</text>
	<select name="isoseq" description="Select type of isomiR" help="isoseq">
		<option text="addition3">3 addition</option>
		<option text="trimmed5">5 trimming</option>
		<option text="trimmed3">3 trimming</option>
		<option text="mut">nt substitution</option>
	</select>
	<text description="Start position in nt-substitution" value="1" help="start">
		<name>start</name>
	</text>
	<text description="End position in nt-substitution" value="8" help="end">
		<name>end</name>
	</text>
	<text description="Trimming size" value="3" help="size">
		<name>size</name>
	</text>
	<text description="Addition size" value="3" help="sizead">
		<name>sizead</name>
	</text>
	<text description="Contribution Cut-Off" value="10" help="cof">
		<name>cof</name>
	</text>
	<select description="Applied probabilistic model" name="error" help="error">
		<option text="zscore">zscore</option>
		<option text="none">...</option>
	</select>
	<checkbox description="NT bias significance" help="pvaluent">
		<name>pvaluent</name>
	</checkbox>
	
	<help id="len">
		<desc>Filter the sequences according to a length cut-off</desc>
	</help>
	<help id="freq">
		<desc>Filter the sequences according to a frequency cut-off</desc>
	</help>
	<help id="start">
		<desc>Select the first position in the reference miRNA for the analysis of nt-substitution variants</desc>
	</help>
	<help id="end">
		<desc>Select the last position in the reference miRNA for the analysis of nt-substitution variants</desc>
	</help>
	<help id="size">
		<desc>Select the number of positions to consider in the trimming variants. The default value of 3 considers 3 positions upstream and 3 positions downstream of the reference 5'-end or 3'-end miRNA</desc>
	</help>
	<help id="sizead">
		<desc>Select the number of nucleotides to be considered in the 3' addition variants</desc>
	</help>
	<help id="DB">
		<desc>Select all sequences mapped onto a miRNA-like database. In the
			case, the annotation was done usign SeqBuster Server, you can choose
between: miRNA or misRNA (miRNA star) or the same name chosen when annotating with the stand-alone version.</desc>
</help>
	
	<help id="isoseq">
		<desc>Select the type of variants to consider in the analysis: extensions of the 3'-end of the miRNA, different 5'-terminus, different 3'-terminus or nt-substitution</desc>
	</help>
	<help id="cof">
		<desc>Select a cut-off value. This value is used to filter the isomiRs contributing in more than a specific percentage to the total of sequences annotated in the same miRNA locus</desc>
	</help>
	<help id="zscore">
		<desc>Select "Z-score" to apply a statistical method to exclude sequencing errors as the possible cause of the nucleotide modifications (Dohm et al., 2008, Nu Ac Res., 36 (16): e105)</desc>
	</help>
	<help id="pvaluent">
		<desc>check this box to calculate a p-value to highlight a significant bias in the type of nucleotide of the reference miRNA involved in the nt-substitution and trimming variants; or the type of nucleotide being added in the 3' addition variants</desc>
	</help>
</param>
